{
    "subject": "resource/Amir_Mirza_Hekmati",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Arizona",
    "human_readable": "Amir Mirza Hekmati was born in Arizona.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9534225463867188,
            "question": "Where was Amir Mirza Hekmati born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7484966516494751,
            "question": "What state is known for being home to Amir Mirza Hekmati's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7378613352775574,
            "question": "What is the significance of Arizona in relation to Amir Mirza Hekmati?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7289590835571289,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Amir Mirza Hekmati's birthplace and his profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5846002101898193,
            "question": "How does Amir Mirza Hekmati's birthplace influence his identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5042349100112915,
            "question": "Are there any other notable individuals born in Arizona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4927709698677063,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Amir Mirza Hekmati's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4774535000324249,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Amir Mirza Hekmati?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15301622450351715,
            "question": "What are some famous landmarks or locations in Arizona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06821855157613754,
            "question": "What are some unique characteristics of Arizona's culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amir Mirza Hekmati was born in Arizona.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8753_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some famous landmarks or locations in Arizona?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8753_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Amir Mirza Hekmati?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8753_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Amir Mirza Hekmati's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8753_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8753_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Amir Mirza Hekmati was indeed born in Arizona, with two of them specifying that he was born in Flagstaff, Arizona (in 1983) and one stating that he was born in the US state of Arizona."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Amir Mirza-Hekmati was born in Arizona, which supports the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}